I've been thinking even more about LLM
tokens and I've come up with a few
little diagrams to explain how they
work. Let's say you pass an input of
hello to an LLM. That text hello won't
be read by the LLM itself. It will be
turned into a token or if you're using
the technical term encoded into a token.
The LLM will then produce output tokens
which will then be decoded into text.
And so the LLM is doing all of its
thinking in terms of these numeric
tokens. Here the whole process looks
like this. We have some input text that
gets turned into tokens. The LLM does a
little bit of processing here and we
start getting output tokens produced
which are immediately decoded. And the
input and output tokens, this is what
you get build for because that's the
closest representation of what's
happening in the LLM's brain. If you
enjoyed these, then I'll be sharing more
of them. So follow along so you can keep
in touch and I'll see you very